export const math_preboard_prime = [
    {
        choices: ["18:25", "10:9", "1:2", "9:10"],
        correctAnswer: "9:10",
        question: "A rectangular sheet of cardboard is cut down by 10% of its length and 20% of its width. What is the ratio of the new area and the original?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Portal to portal pay", "Call end pay", "Back wages", "Call back pay"],
        correctAnswer: "Call back pay",
        question: "A term used to describe payment of an employee wherein an employee is called back to work after his regular days work.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["0.72", "0.85", "0.81", "0.65"],
        correctAnswer: "0.65",
        question: "Find the length of the arc of the curve y=ln cosx from x=0 to x=pi/8.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["P10000", "P10500", "P9500", "P8500"],
        correctAnswer: "P10500",
        question: "If the loan was for 15 months at 16.8% interest a year and the repayment on a loan was P12100.00, how much was the principal?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["8", "12", "16", "2"],
        correctAnswer: "16",
        question: "Charlie mixed blue and red paint in the ratio 3:5 instead of 5:3 when he prepared 24 liters of violet paint. How many liters of the blue paint should he add to obtain the shade he wants?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["The tangent is positive", "The cosine is negative", "The cotangent is positive", "The sine is negative"],
        correctAnswer: "The cosine is negative",
        question: "Which is true regarding the signs of the natural functions for angles between 90 deg to 180 deg?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Secant", "Cevian", "Euclidian", "Newton Line"],
        correctAnswer: "Cevian",
        question: "Any line segment joining a vertex of a triangle to a point on the opposite side is called as.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["5", "more than 5", "4", "3"],
        correctAnswer: "5",
        question: "Before a registered Mechanical Engineer be allowed to take the Proffesional Mechanical Engineer Licensure Examination, he must have ___ years of practice as a registered mechanical engineer.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["30deg", "75deg", "60deg", "45deg"],
        correctAnswer: "30deg",
        question: "An angle is half its supplement, What is its complement.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["the inverse-square law", "the law of tangents", "the law of sines", "the law of cosines"],
        correctAnswer: "the law of cosines",
        question: "To find the angle of a triangle, given only the lengths of the sides, one would use",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["20%", "15%", "10%", "25%"],
        correctAnswer: "10%",
        question: "A 40 liter salt solution is 25% salt. If 10 liters of water are added to it, what percent of the new solution is salt?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["66", "29", "36", "102"],
        correctAnswer: "102",
        question: "A ball rolling on an inclined plane rolls 15cm in the first second. If in every second therafter it rolls 7cm more than in the preceding second, how far will it will roll in 4 seconds.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["40", "20", "30", "25"],
        correctAnswer: "30",
        question: "Twenty-five workers can make 50 engines in 2 weeks, How many engines will be made by 30 workers in 7 days assuming that they work at the same rate?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["8", "14", "6", "12"],
        correctAnswer: "14",
        question: "The unit digit of a two-digit number exceeds the ten digits by 4. What is the largets sum of the digits among all two-digit numbers that satisfy the given condition.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Specific volume is zero", "Vapor pressure is zero", "Internal energy is negative", "Entropy is non-zero"],
        correctAnswer: "Internal energy is negative",
        question: "Which of the following is true for water at reference temperature where the enthalpy is zero?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["0", "e", "1/e", "1"],
        correctAnswer: "e",
        question: "Find the value of x when the function y=lnx/x is ata maximum value.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["3:24", "24:3", "45:24", "75:54"],
        correctAnswer: "45:24",
        question: "Find the two numbers in the ratio 15:8 and differs by 21.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Nonagon", "Heptagon", "Hexagon", "Pentagon"],
        correctAnswer: "Nonagon",
        question: "What is a regular polygon that has 27 diagonals?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["8", "4", "3", "2"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
        question: "If the area of circle was increased four time, then how many times was its circumference increased?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Quadratic Case", "Ambiguous Case", "Extraneous Case", "Conditional Case"],
        correctAnswer: "Ambiguous Case",
        question: "This is the case of the summation of a solution of a plane triangle where the given data leads to two solutions. How do you call this case.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["P4200.00", "P4,300.00", "P4315.00", "P4,254.00"],
        correctAnswer: "",
        question: "P400.00 are deposited at the end of every year for eight years in an account that earned 8% annual effective interest. How much after 8 years would the account be worth?(walay answer)",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["fourth power", "first power", "second power", "third power"],
        correctAnswer: "fourth power",
        question: "The moment of inertia of any plane figure can be expressed in units of length to the ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["33.21", "13.23", "31.32", "21.33"],
        correctAnswer: "21.33",
        question: "Find the area bounded by the parabola y^2=4x and the line x=4.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["66", "270", "135", "can&amp;amp;#39;t determine from the given information"],
        correctAnswer: "270",
        question: "Find the area of a trapezoid whos median and altitude have lengths 15 and 18, respectively.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Periodic inventory system", "Gross of goods sold", "Perpetual inventory system", "Physical inventory system"],
        correctAnswer: "Gross of goods sold",
        question: "The difference between the starting and the ending inventory valuations, a term that represents and inventory account adjust is called.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["potential difference", "current", "power", "voltage"],
        correctAnswer: "current",
        question: "In electricity, how do you call the rate of chargge flow?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["7!", "5!", "6!", "8!"],
        correctAnswer: "7!",
        question: "Eight children are to be seated in a round table. In how many ways can they be seated?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["17%", "34%", "20%", "40%"],
        correctAnswer: "17%",
        question: "If the length of rectangle is increase by 30% and the width of the rectangle is decrease by 10%. then the area is increased by____.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["work", "force", "power", "momentum"],
        correctAnswer: "power",
        question: "the first derivative of kinetic energy with respect to time",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["2 is not a prime number because it is even", "1 is a prime number", "The product of the first 10 prime numbers must have a unit digit of 0", "It is possible for two consecutive integers greater thatn 2 to be both prime numbers"],
        correctAnswer: "The product of the first 10 prime numbers must have a unit digit of 0",
        question: "Which of the following is true?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Sinking fund factor and uniform series compound amount factor are reciprocals", "Capital recovery factor equals sinking fund factor plus the interest rate.", "Capital recovery factor and sinking fund factor are reciprocals.", "Single payment comound amount factor and single payment present worth factor are reciprocals."],
        correctAnswer: "Capital recovery factor and sinking fund factor are reciprocals.",
        question: "Which of the following relationships between compound interest factors is NOT correct?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["16", "4", "8", "2"],
        correctAnswer: "4",
        question: "Two coins are tossed. How many possible outcomes are there?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["physical inventory", "material count", "none of the above", "material update"],
        correctAnswer: "physical inventory",
        question: "Consists of the actual counting or determination of the actual quantity of the materials on hand as of a given date",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["2(N-5)", "N+5", "2N+5", "2N+10"],
        correctAnswer: "2N+10",
        question: "Roberto was N years old 5 years ago. If David is now twice as old as Roberto, then David&amp;amp;#39;s age now can be represented as ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["90", "30", "360", "60"],
        correctAnswer: "360",
        question: "How many numbers of 4 different digits each greater thatn 5000 can be formed from the digits 1,2,3,4,5,6,7? ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["P180,000", "P182,000", "P186,300", "P186,340"],
        correctAnswer: "P186,340",
        question: "Mr. Ramas borrowed P140,000 at 10% for three years. How much did she pay in all?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Cevian", "Secant", "Newton Line", "Euclidian"],
        correctAnswer: "Cevian",
        question: "Any line segment joining a vertex of a triangle to a point on the opposite side is called as:",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["P13,500.00", "P12,681.00", "P150,250.00", "P21,931.00"],
        correctAnswer: "P12,681.00",
        question: "What is the present worth of P27,000 due in 6 years if money is worth 13% and is compounded semi-annually.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["34", "17", "20", "16"],
        correctAnswer: "",
        question: "A piece of rope was cut into two so that the lengths of the 2 pieces are in the ratio 7:9. If one was longer by 6m, how long was each piece?(walay answer)",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["21", "25", "9", "18"],
        correctAnswer: "21",
        question: "Determine the absolute value of resultant vector of the following vectors:&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;F1=4i+7j+6k; F2=9i+2j+11k; F3=5i-3j-8K",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["2.0cm", "2.5cm", "1.75cm", "2.25cm"],
        correctAnswer: "1.75cm",
        question: "A 70kg man jumps off a raft whose base area is 4 sq. m floating in a freshwater lake, By how much does the raft rise?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Bending stress", "Tensile stress", "Shearing stress", "Compressive stress"],
        correctAnswer: "Shearing stress",
        question: "Structural steel elements subjected to torsion develop",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["The ratio of gross margin to operating, sales, and administrative expenses.", "The ratio of current assets(exclusive of inventory) to total current liabilities", "The ratio of owners equity to total current liabilities.", "The ratio of all assets to total liabilities"],
        correctAnswer: "The ratio of current assets(exclusive of inventory) to total current liabilities",
        question: "What is the acid test ratio.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["earning value", "money market", "profit and loss statement", "liquidated damage"],
        correctAnswer: "profit and loss statement",
        question: "Grand total of the assets and operational capability of a corporation",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Invesments", "Depreciation", "Bonding", "Amortization"],
        correctAnswer: "Amortization",
        question: "Manner of liquidating a debt by installment usually at equal interverals of time.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["trade union", "employees club", "employes union", "company union"],
        correctAnswer: "trade union",
        question: "An organization of the workers of the particular trade or craft whose primary aim is to improve the social and economics status of its members",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Moment", "Scalar", "Tensor", "Resultant"],
        correctAnswer: "Resultant",
        question: "What is the name of the vector that represent a two vectors.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["P808,811", "P905,902", "P801,900", "P810,000"],
        correctAnswer: "P810,000",
        question: "A house and lot can be acquired a downpayment of P500,000 and a yearly payment of P1000 at the end of each year for a period of 10 years, starting at the end of 5years from the date of purchase. If the money is worth 14% compounded annually, what is the cash price of the property.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["15.2 N/m^3", "76.3N/m^3", "98.2 N/m^3", "9.04N/m^3"],
        correctAnswer: "15.2 N/m^3",
        question: "If the density of a gas is 0.003 slug/ft^3, what is the specific weight of the gas?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["5%", "8%", "7%", "6%"],
        correctAnswer: "8%",
        question: "What is the rate of interest charged on a loan of P7500 for 2 years if the interest paid was P1200.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["5.36", "4.08", "5.90", "4.60"],
        correctAnswer: "",
        question: "A circle with center ate (-3,1) and radius 4 tangent to another circle with center ate (4,-4). Find the radius of the other circle.(walay answer)",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["It is always greater than zero", "It is temperature dependent", "It is always less than zero", "It is always zero"],
        correctAnswer: "It is always zero",
        question: "During an adiabatic, internally reversible process, what is true about the change of entropy",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["2.5%", "3.12%", "3.75%", "1.2%"],
        correctAnswer: "2.5%",
        question: "A man borrowed P2000 from a bank and aggreed to pay the loan at the end of 1 year. The bank discounted the loan ang give P1950. Determine the rate of discount.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["-4", "2", "4", "-2"],
        correctAnswer: "-4",
        question: "Determine the slope of the curve y=-x^2 at the point (2.3).",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Deca", "Hecto", "Nano", "Exa"],
        correctAnswer: "Deca",
        question: "A prefix denoting the multiple of 10 times any of the physical units of the system international.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["70", "65", "67.5", "72.5"],
        correctAnswer: "70",
        question: "A student&amp;amp;#39;s grad on the first of 7 quizzes in Math was 55. However on each succesive quiz her score was 5 more than on the preceding one, What was the average of the seven quizzes?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["64", "7", "8", "56"],
        correctAnswer: "56",
        question: "In a party, each guest must bring a gift for every other guest. If there were 8 guests, how many gifts were brought?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["3:30:66", "3:06:36", "3:03:66", "3:36:36"],
        correctAnswer: "3:06:36",
        question: "It is now between 3 and 4 o&amp;amp;#39;clock. In twenty minutes, the minute hand will be as much as the hour hand as it is behind it. What is the time now?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["sunk cost", "integral cost", "variable cost", "increment cost"],
        correctAnswer: "integral cost",
        question: "Cost which arise as a result of a change in operation or policy",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["12%", "10%", "9%", "8%"],
        correctAnswer: "10%",
        question: "Laura borrowed P5000 to her friend Zeny. She paid P1200 as interest for 2 years. What was the rate of interest?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["a random point", "an event", "a sample space", "a finite set"],
        correctAnswer: "an event",
        question: "What is a possible outcome of an experiment called?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["public", "equitable", "private", "pure"],
        correctAnswer: "private",
        question: "type of ownership in business when individuals exercise and enjoy the right in their own interest.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["5x+3y+7=0", "3x-5y-7=0", "5x-3y-7=0", "3x+5y+7=0"],
        correctAnswer: "",
        question: "What is equation of the passing through A(2,-1) and B(-3,-4)?(walay answer)",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["90deg", "270deg", "360deg", "150deg"],
        correctAnswer: "360deg",
        question: "What is the sum of the measure of all interior angles of a trapezoid.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Magnetic Flux", "Capacitance", "Inductance", "Magnetic Induction"],
        correctAnswer: "Magnetic Induction",
        question: "Telsa is a unit of which of the following.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["15", "10", "17", "13"],
        correctAnswer: "10",
        question: "The sum of five consecutive numbers is 75. What is the average of the smallest and largest numbers?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["5mx25m", "5mx15m", "25mx50m", "3mx15m"],
        correctAnswer: "5mx25m",
        question: "A rectangular room is to contain 125 sq. meters of flooring. If the length is to be five times its width, what should its dimensions be?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Obtuse", "Isosceles", "Right", "Acute"],
        correctAnswer: "Right",
        question: "If the sides of a triangle are in the ratio of 5:12:13, then the triangle is ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["160", "280", "80", "120"],
        correctAnswer: "280",
        question: "Suppose a ball rebounds three-fourths the distance it falls. If it is dropped from a height of 40 feet, how far does it travel before coming to rest?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["P4200", "P2800", "P3500", "P5000"],
        correctAnswer: "P4200",
        question: "Mr. Charlie an artist was paid P7000 for the month of June, 40% of which was overtime pay. What was the amount of his regular pay?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["15", "12", "10", "6"],
        correctAnswer: "10",
        question: "A group of six members gathered for a special meeting. Each member has the shake hands with all the other members. Find the total number of the hand shakes made?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["4:1", "1:3", "4:3", "1:1"],
        correctAnswer: "4:3",
        question: "If mangoes are thrice as expensive as bananas, and bananas are one-fourth as expensive as pineapples, what is the ratio of the price of one mango to one pineapple?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["132,444", "128,413", "122,444", "124,164"],
        correctAnswer: "124,164",
        question: "How much money would have to be invested to have 200,000 at the end of 5 years at a 10% compound interest rate?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["commutative", "closure", "associativity", "distributive property"],
        correctAnswer: "associativity",
        question: "Which property of whole numbers is used to justify the statement (2+3)=4=4+(3+2) ?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["50", "40", "8", "10"],
        correctAnswer: "10",
        question: "If there are 8 to 10 trays to a box, what is the maximum number of trays in 5 boxes?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Annulus", "Annular", "Torus", "Circoloid"],
        correctAnswer: "Torus",
        question: "How do you call a ring shaped surface of solid obtained by rotating a circle about a coplanar line that does not intersect.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Commonwealth Act 594", "Commonwealth Act 394", "Commonwealth Act 294", "Commonwealth Act 8394"],
        correctAnswer: "Commonwealth Act 294",
        question: "Which of the following Commonwealth Acts is known as the oldest Mechanical Engineering Law?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Precipitation", "Hydration", "Saturation", "Dehydration"],
        correctAnswer: "Precipitation",
        question: "Adding more solute to an alraedy saturated solution will cause the excess solute to settle to the bottom of the container. What is this  process called.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["All rhombuses are squares", "All rectangles are parallelograms", "All square are rhombuses", "All rhombuses are parallelograms"],
        correctAnswer: "All rhombuses are squares",
        question: "Which of the following statements about quadrilaterals is not true?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["an epicycloid", "a hypocycloid", "a helix", "a cycloid"],
        correctAnswer: "a helix",
        question: "What type of curve is generated by a point whch moves in uniform circular motion about an axis, while traveling with a constant speed, parallel to the axis?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["80 deg F", "85.6 deg F", "81.5 deg F", "82.5 deg F"],
        correctAnswer: "85.6 deg F",
        question: "An object reads from 120 deg F to 95 deg F in half an hour when surrounded by air whose temperature is 80 deg F. Find the temperature at the end of another half an hour.&amp;lt;BR/&amp;gt;",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["99,400", "22,738", "35, 785", "66,745"],
        correctAnswer: "22,738",
        question: "How maaaaaats! would be accumulated in the sinking fund that is to amount to P50,000 at the end of 18 years if interest is nominal 4.4% compounded  monthly.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["P245,775.19", "P144,775.19", "P542.775.91", "P254,775.19"],
        correctAnswer: "",
        question: "A machine was purchased under these terms. P30000 down and P5000 each month fora 5 years. If money is worth 12% compounded monthly, what is the cash price of the machine?(walay answer)",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["6", "8", "12", "16"],
        correctAnswer: "16",
        question: "Bacteria culture grows exponentially so that the initial number has double in 2.5 hours. How many times the initial number will be present after 10hrs.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["A water pipe", "Bridge beam", "A cutting tool", "A ball bearing"],
        correctAnswer: "A cutting tool",
        question: "Which of the following would most likely require as steel containing 0.6 % carbon that has been spheroidize, cold-drawn, and slightly tempered?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["x=-y^2+2", "x=4y^2-2", "y=4x^2-2", "y=-x^2+1"],
        correctAnswer: "y=-x^2+1",
        question: "Which of the following parabolas open downward?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Labor", "People", "Technology", "Machine"],
        correctAnswer: "Labor",
        question: "Under the code of ethics, the mechanical engineer should recognize _____ as one of the major resources of our country.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Cost of producing a product or rendering a service", "Total annual overhead assigned to a unit of production", "As series of equal payments occuring at equal periods of time", "Earned interest due ate the end of each interest period."],
        correctAnswer: "As series of equal payments occuring at equal periods of time",
        question: "An annuity is define as ",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Myriagon", "Octacondagon", "Chilliagon", "Hectogon"],
        correctAnswer: "Myriagon",
        question: "How do you call a polygon with 10,000 sides",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["depreciation cost", "indirest cost", "obsolescence", "fixed cost"],
        correctAnswer: "obsolescence",
        question: "the reduction value and marketability due to competition from newest prducts",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Octacondagon", "Chilliagon", "Hectogon", "Myriagon"],
        correctAnswer: "Myriagon",
        question: "How do you call a polygon with 10000 sides.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Identical salvage value", "Different equivalent uniform annual cash flow", "Identical equivalent uniform annual cash flow", "Different salvage value"],
        correctAnswer: "Different equivalent uniform annual cash flow",
        question: "What must two invesment with the same present worth and unequal lives have?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Rotation", "Twist", "Angular distortion", "Volume distortion"],
        correctAnswer: "Twist",
        question: "Which is of the following is the not a basic component of motion of a fluid element.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["50kph", "48kph", "47.5kph", "52.5kph"],
        correctAnswer: "50kph",
        question: "Diego drove ate a 45 kph for 4 hours and then at 60kph for 2 hours. What was his average speed for the whole trip?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["12", "13", "18", "11"],
        correctAnswer: "18",
        question: "The sum of the three numbers in arithmetic progression is 39. If these numbers are increased by 1, 5 and 12 respectively the new nubmers will be in geometric progression, Find the second term of the geometric progression?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["MPE", "CPM", "RME", "PME"],
        correctAnswer: "CPM",
        question: "Minimum grade mechanical engineer required in the maintenance of a 200 kW diesel power plant",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["book value", "equity", "liquidated damages", "profit and loss statement"],
        correctAnswer: "profit and loss statement",
        question: "Financial statement which compare the revenues of the period with the expensive incurred to gain those revenues.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["14", "28", "7", "35"],
        correctAnswer: "14",
        question: "How long must the side of the square be in order that its area be four times the area of a square whos side is 7?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["power", "voltage", "resonance", "current "],
        correctAnswer: "voltage",
        question: "how do you call an energy required  to move 1 coulomb of charge through an element?",
        topic: "NA"
    },
    {
        choices: ["Arc", "Acre", "Hectare", "Are"],
        correctAnswer: "Are",
        question: "An SI unit of area equal to 100 sq. meters.",
        topic: "NA"
    },
]